<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeroMe</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="turtlePower">
        <item>Ninja Turtles</item>
        <item>Leonardo and his brothers were once ordinary turtles: when they were infants,
            they were adopted from a pet store by Hamato Yoshi. When their soon to be
            father walked passed a strange man, a Kraangdroid, he felt something odd about
            him and followed. Unfortunately, Yoshi gave away his position when he accidentally
            stepped on a brown rat's tail. The Kraang found him and attempted to kill him,
            but Yoshi fought back hard. In the end, the Kraang dropped the canister of
            Mutagen they were holding, causing the turtles and Yoshi to mutate. Yoshi,
            having to have stepped on that rat, thus mutated into a humanoid brown rat by
            the name of "Splinter", while Leo and his brothers, after coming in contact
            with Splinter when he was human, mutated into humanoid turtles. .</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="lightning">
        <item>Thor</item>
        <item>Thor Odinson is the current king of Asgard, a founding member of the Avengers,
            and the God of Thunder. When all his irresponsible behavior restarted a
            conflict between Asgard and Jotunheim which had threatened his homeland,
            Thor was then denied the right to become King and was then stripped of his
            power and banished by his father Odin onto the Earth. While exiled on Earth,
            Thor learned humility, found love in Jane Foster, and helped to save all his
            new friends from a destructive threat sent by his own jealous adoptive
            brother Loki, sacrificing his own life to save all of the innocents in
            the process. Due to his selfless act of sacrifice, Thor redeemed himself
            in his father's eyes and was granted his power once more which he then
            used to defeat Loki's schemes of genocide.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="flight">
        <item>Superman</item>
        <item> Sent as a baby to Earth from the dying planet Krypton, Kal-El was
            adopted by Martha and Jonathan Kent of Smallville, Kansas. Growing up as
            Clark Kent, he devoted his life to helping others with the abilities he
            developed from Earth's sun. Moving to Metropolis, he became Superman,
            while still maintaining his secret identity as Clark Kent, who works at
            the Daily Planet newspaper.Superman possesses the ability to fly under his own power,
            incredible strength and near invulnerability, as he can only be harmed by the
            element Kryptonite. His eyes can emit bursts of heat, while vision ranges from
            the microscopic to the telescopic. His vision is also capable of a broader
            spectrum than human eyes, able to see x-rays and radio waves. He can hear faint
            sounds amongst a bustle of noises by concentrating. His lungs are capable
            of holding air for long periods of time in environments without oxygen, and
            the ability to compress this air and exhale it in a freezing capacity.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="webslinging">
        <item>Spider-Man</item>
        <item>Bitten by a radioactive spider, high school student Peter Parker gained the speed,
            strength and powers of a spider. Adopting the name Spider-Man,
            Peter hoped to start a career using his new ... more. ... Amazing Spider-Man
            Peter Benjamin Parker is a high school student and a superhero with spider-like abilities,
            fighting crime as his alter ego Spider-Man. After receiving his abilities from
            a spider's bite, Parker chose to protect Queens from crime with his powers,
            juggling all of his superhero duties and the demands of his high school life.
            Despite his best efforts to keep his identity secret from the world, he was found
            and recruited by Tony Stark in the Avengers Civil War, while gaining a new suit
            and technology in exchange for his help.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="laservision">
        <item>Cyclops</item>
        <item>As a teen, Scott came under the foster care of Jack Winters, a mutant criminal
            also known as Jack O' Diamonds. During this time, Scott began to suffer from
            severe headaches and was sent to a specialist who discovered lenses made of
            ruby quartz could correct the problem.Soon after, Scott's powerful optic beams
            erupted from his eyes, demolishing a crane in the process and causing the crane
            to drop its payload toward a crowd of people. Luckily, Scott managed to save
            them by obliterating the object with another blast. However, the people believed
            that Scott was trying to kill them and rallied up an angry mob.
            Scott managed to flee by boarding a freight train.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="superstrength">
        <item>Hulk</item>
        <item>Robert Bruce Banner, M.D., Ph.D is a renowned scientist who was highly
            respected for all his work in the fields of Biochemistry, Nuclear Physics,
            and Gamma Radiation. Having been tasked by General Thaddeus Ross to find
            a way to recreate the Super Soldier Serum which had originated Captain
            America, Banner conducted an experiment with Gamma Radiation. However
            when an exposure to high levels of Gamma Radiation instead of Vita Radiation
            went awry, the mild-mannered scientist had found that when angered or
            provoked, he would then transform into the huge rage-fueled and nearly
            mindless green-skinned monster known as Hulk.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
